Guide to the Ramón Hernández Tejano Music Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Artist Files, 1922-2019, undated
  - Male Artist Files
    - Raymond S. Gonzales y Rayo, 2000, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Raymond S. Gonzales y Rayo - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Rick Gonzales & the Choice, 1988, 1990, undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Rick Gonzales & the Choice - Clippings, 1990-1991, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Rick Gonzales & the Choice - Promotional material, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Mounted photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Mounted photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Concert and event publicity, 2009-2016, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Ramón Hernández material, 1986, 2010, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Album covers, 1965, 2008, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Clippings, 1986-2018 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Clippings, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Rudy Tee Gonzales and the Reno Bops - Audiovisual material, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Alberto Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Angel Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Arturo "Sauce" Gonzalez, 1987, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Arturo "Sauce" Gonzalez - Clippings, 1991-2018, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Arturo "Sauce" Gonzalez - Audiovisual material, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Balde Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Christian "Buddy" Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - David Gonzáles, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Eddie Gonzalez - Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Eddie Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Eddie Gonzalez - Clippings, 1994-2017, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Francisco Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Freddy Gonzalez y Los Super Unidos, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - George Gonzalez, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Gustavo Gonzalez, 1996, 1998, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - J.J. Gonzalez, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Jesse "Chuy" Gonzalez, 2011, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Jesse "Chuy" Gonzalez - Clippings, 2017, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Jimmy Gonzalez y Grupo Mazz, 2000, 2008, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Jimmy Gonzalez y Grupo Mazz - Clippings, 1991-2018, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Jimmy Gonzalez y Grupo Mazz - Audiovisual material, 2017 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Joe Jo Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Pete Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Ramón González Mora, 2000, 2010, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Raul Gonzalez, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - René Gonzalez, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Wally Gonzalez, 1993-2012, undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Wally Gonzalez - Audiovisual material, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Xavier Gonzalez, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Good Times Band, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Los Gorrioncillos de Uvalde, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Los Grandes, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Los Grandes de Tejas, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Eliseo Grenet, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Bob Grever, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Robert Grijalva, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Grupo Aguila, 1996, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Grupo Alamo, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Grupo Animo, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Grupo Arrko, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Grupo Badd, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Grupo Badd - Audiovisual material, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Grupo Blanco, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Grupo Caliente y Marky Lee, 2003, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Grupo Calle Sol, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Grupo Coahuila, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Grupo CoraSoul, undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Grupo Creacion, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Grupo Cristal, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Grupo Daño, 2014, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Grupo de Oro, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Grupo Division, 1997, undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Grupo E'lusion, 1996, undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Grupo Elite Real, undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Grupo Estrella, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Grupo Excito, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Grupo Fantasma, 2008-2015 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Grupo Illusion, undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Grupo Inspiracion, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Grupo Kalidad, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Grupo Kalor, undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Grupo Ladron, undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Grupo Latino, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Grupo Lazzo, undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Grupo Luna, undated (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Grupo Maldad, [2011], undated (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Grupo Medaya, undated (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Grupo Medaya - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Grupo Milagro, [2000]-2001, undated (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Grupo Milagro - Audiovisual material, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Grupo Ondo, undated (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Grupo Oro, undated (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Grupo Pasion, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Grupo Poder '93, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Grupo Presencia, undated (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Grupo Primmor, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Grupo Recuerdo, undated (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Grupo Respeto, undated (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Grupo Roble, 2001, undated (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Grupo Rumores, undated (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Grupo Sierra, undated (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Grupo Universo, undated (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Grupo Vida, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Grupo Vida - Clippings, 2000-2015, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Grupo Villela, 2014 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Grupo Vision, 2013-2014, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Grupo Vizion, 2014, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Grupo Voltaje, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Grupo Zaga, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Los Guadalupanos, 1997, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Gary Guajardo, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Jimmy Guajardo, 2009-2010 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - La Guerra Musical, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Ernesto Guerra, 2005-2010 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Frank Guerra, 1989, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Henry Guerra, 1991-1995, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Manny Guerra - Photographs, [1993], undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Manny Guerra - Business records, 1986-1990 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Manny Guerra - Ramón Hernández material, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Manny Guerra - Clippings, 1990-2009, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Michael Guerra, 2012, 2014 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Mike Guerra, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Rudy Guerra - Photographs, 1987, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Rudy Guerra: Rudy Guerra Ministries, undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Rudy Guerra - Concert and event publicity, 1986, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Rudy Guerra - Album covers, 1988, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Rudy Guerra - Ramón Hernández material, 1987, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Rudy Guerra - Clippings, 2008, undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Rudy Guerra - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Eddie Guerrero, undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Emilio Guerrero - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Emilio Guerrero, undated (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Emilio Guerrero - Ramón Hernández material, 1986, undated (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Emilio Guerrero - Clippings, 1976-1986, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Hugo Guerrero - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Hugo Guerrero - Concert and event publicity, 2017-2018, undated (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Hugo Guerrero - Ramón Hernández material, 1989, undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Hugo Guerrero - Clippings, 1989, 2018, undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Hugo Guerrero - Promotional material, undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Joe Guerrero, undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Juan Guerrero y Los Sheekanos, undated (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Leo Guerrero, 2018, undated (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Louie Guerrero, undated (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Manuel Guerrero, undated (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Manuel Guerrero - Clippings, 1991, 2007, undated (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Nico Guerrero y Sus Tropicanos, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Tony "Ham" Guerrero - Photographs, 1968, 1974, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Tony "Ham" Guerrero - Publicity, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Tony "Ham" Guerrero - Ramón Hernández material, 2009, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Tony "Ham" Guerrero - Clippings, 1993-2011 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Adrian Gutierrez, 2016-2017 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Dave Gutierrez y Orquesta, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Eugenio Gutierrez, 2009, 2012, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Johnny Gi-Tar Gutierrez, 1992, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Jose Angel Gutierrez, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Ray Gutierrez, 2014, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Ricardo Gutiérrez y Rival, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Roland Gutierrez, 2014 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Ruben R. Gutíerrez, 2014 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Salome Gutiérrez - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Salome Gutiérrez - Lyrics, 1947, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Salome Gutiérrez - Ramón Hernández material, 1987-1992 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Salome Gutiérrez - Clippings, 1989, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Sergio Gutierrez, 1995, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Sergio Gutierrez - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Carlos Guzmán - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Carlos Guzmán, 1983, 2017, undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Carlos Guzmán - Ramón Hernández material, undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Carlos Guzmán - Clippings, 1977-2015, undated (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Carlos Guzmán - Promotional material, undated (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Joel Guzman, 1995-2012, undated (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Jorge Guzman, 2008, undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Ricky Guzman III & the All-Stars, 2008, undated (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Benny Harp, 2014 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - John Harvey, 1987, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Bruce Hathaway, 1985-2014, undated (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Hecho en Mexico, 2007-2008 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Henry & the Playboys, undated (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - La Herencia Chicana, undated (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Hermanos Chavarria, undated (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Hermanos Dávila, undated (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Hermanos De Leon, 2012, undated (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Los Hermanos Farias - Clippings, 2011, 2013 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Los Hermanos Farias - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Hermanos Layton, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Los Hermanos Lujan, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Los Hermanos Medina, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Hermanos Mungia (North Texas Boyz), undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Los Hermanos Riós, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Hermanos Salinas, 2013, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Los Hermanos Tovar, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Hermanos Treviño, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Los Hermanos Villarreal, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Abel Hernandez, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Andy Hernandez, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Anthony Hernandez, 2010, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Bubba Hernandez, 2012, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Fabian Hernandez, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Fidel Hernandez, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Homer Hernandez, 2000, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Homer Hernandez - Clippings, 2000, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Ian Matthew Hernandez, 2015, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Jesse Hernandez, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Jesus "Crazy Chuy" Hernandez, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - John Hernandez and the Top Shelf Band, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Johnny Hernandez - Photographs, undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Johnny Hernandez, 1997-2013, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Johnny Hernandez - Albums, 1988, 1992, undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Johnny Hernandez - Clippings, 1986-2011, undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Johnny Hernandez - Audiovisual material, [1988] (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Childhood, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Early career, 1967-1977, undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Portraits, 2000, undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Publicity photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Publicity photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Performances (1 of 2), 1985-2007, undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Performances (2 of 2), 1985-2007, undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Events, 1992-2001 undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Celebration of Life, 60th Birthday Celebration, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Snapshots, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Photocopied portraits of band members, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Mounted photographs ( 1 of 2), 1979-1998, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Mounted photographs ( 2 of 2), 1979-1998, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Posters, [1991-1992], undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Photographs - Personal - Family - Ady Hernandez (son), undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Amelia DeLeon Hernandez (mother), 1987-1999, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Antonio "Top" Hernandez (brother), 2007, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Cris Hernandez (wife), undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Gilbert Hernandez (brother), 2018, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Ike Hernandez (son), undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Ivan Hernandez (son), undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Jesse "Chuy" Hernandez (brother), undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Jimmy "La Avispa" Hernandez (brother), 2018, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Porfirio "Quila" Hernandez (brother), 1973, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal - Family - Salvador Hernandez (father), undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Personal, 2001, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Correspondence to Little Joe, 1988-1993 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Correspondence from Little Joe, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Concert and event publicity, 1983-2016, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Concert and event publicity, 1984-1016, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Backstage passes, 1990-2009, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Event programs, invitations, and place cards, 1989-2015, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Tours, 1990, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Media appearances, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Publicity, 1979-2002, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Publicity - Biographies and fact sheets, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Publicity - Press releases, 1978, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Publicity - Press kits, [2000], undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Lyrics, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Discography research, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Discographies, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Song credits, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Album covers, 1964-1993, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - ¿Que Paso? album production, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Espiritu album production, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Various album production, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Awards, Proclamations, and Certificates, 1990, 1998, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Little Joe Museum, 1987-2015, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Business records, 1988-1989, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Business ventures, 1993, 2010, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-[1994], undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández material - Correspondence, 1987-2008, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández material - Research, 2004, 2007, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández manuscript - Chapter Drafts (1 of 2), undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández manuscript - Chapter Drafts (2 of 2), undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández manuscript draft - Chapter 1-16, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández manuscript draft - Chapter 17- end, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández manuscript, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Ramón Hernández manuscript - Notes and correspondence, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Other projects based on Little Joe's Life, 2018, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Promotional material - T-Shirt design mock-ups, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Promotional material (1 of 2), undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Promotional material (2 of 2), undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Clippings, 1984-1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Clippings, 1990-1996 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Clippings, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Magazine clippings, 1979-2003, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Clippings (Copies/faxes/printouts), 1977-2015, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Midsized Clippings, 1982-1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Midsized Clippings, 1990-1998 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Midsized Clippings, 2000-2009 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Midsized Clippings, 2010-2018 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Midsized Clippings, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Midsized Clippings - Street Talk clippings, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Magazines (1 of 3), 1985-2016, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Magazines (2 of 3), 1985-2016, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Magazines (3 of 3), 1985-2016, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Audiovisual material - 8-Track Tapes, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Audiovisual material - Cassettes, 1992-1993, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Audiovisual material - CDs, 1992-2001, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Open-reel tape, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Audiovisual material - Videocassettes, 1996, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Audiovisual material - Videocassettes, 1999, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Audiovisual material - Videocassettes, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Oversized material - Photographs, advertisements, album layout draft, and screenprint tranfer, 1991, undated (Box 43)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Oversized material - Mounted posters, undated (Box 44)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Oversized material - Mounted posters, album covers, mounted clippings, 1981-1982, undated (Box 45)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Oversized material - Little Joe's Original Salsa, undated (Box 46)
    - Larry Hernandez, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Mickey Hernandez, 2001, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Miguel Hernandez, 2006, 2011, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Nash Hernandez, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Nathaniel Hernandez, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Nick Hernandez, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Nick Hernandez, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Oscar Hernandez, 1991, 1995, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Raul Hernandez, 1996, 1999, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Ramon "Rocky" Hernandez - Photographs, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Ramon "Rocky" Hernandez, 1988-1994, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Ramon "Rocky" Hernandez - Clippings, 1988, 1990, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Ramon "Rocky" Hernandez - Audiovisual material, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Rocky "Shuffle" Hernandez, 2000-2014, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Rocky "Shuffle" Hernandez - Clippings, 1999-2015 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Roger Hernandez, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Roger Hernandez -Clippings, 2004, 2015, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Roger Hernandez -Audiovisual material, undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Fernando Herrera, 1986, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Johnny Herrera - Photographs, undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Johnny Herrera, 1989, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Johnny Herrera - Clippings, 2000-2010 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Photographs (1 of 3), 1983-1988, undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Photographs (2 of 3), 1983-1988, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Photographs (3 of 3), 1983-1988, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Mounted photographs, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Publicity photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Publicity photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Personal, 1982, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Concert and event publicity, 1984-2017, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Album covers, 1986, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Publicity, 1996-1997, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-1990, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Business correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Clippings, 1990-2014 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Clippings, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Street Talk clippings, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Clipping collages, 1985-989, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Photocopied clippings, 1985-1988 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera -Mounted clippings, 1985, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Magazines, 1998, 2003, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Ramiro "Ram" Herrera - Promotional material, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)